<?xml version="1.0"?>

<PropertyList>
			<title>JWocky's workshop plane</title>

			<key>
				<name>w/W</name>
				<desc>Walk forwards/backwards (on interior views only)</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>Delete</name>
				<desc>toggle thrust reversers</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>g/G</name>
				<desc>raise/lower landing gear</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>B (shift and b)</name>
				<desc>toggle parking brakes</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>pgup/pgdn</name>
				<desc>throttle increase/decrease</desc>
			</key>
            
			<key>
				<name>[/]</name>
				<desc>raise/lower flaps</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>Ctrl-b</name>
				<desc>toggle speed brakes</desc>
			</key>

			<key>
				<name>s</name>
				<desc>hold to start engines</desc>
			</key>

			<text>
				=== Takeoff Procedure ===
				Pre-departure:
				1. - Allocate your fuel, passengers and weight under Equipment/fuel and payload
				   - Once passengers and baggage are loaded and weights defined, close the exit doors
				     and ensure stairways are disconnected
				   - Ensure a complete systems checklist is carried out
				   - Airport operations vehicles should be disconnected from around the aircraft
				   - Taxi away from the terminal with a Pushback truck
				   - In poor weather conditions, or crowded airport aprons, A Followme truck should be used if required

				Departure:
				2. Select 767-300ER/Autostart (or hold s) to get the engines running
				3. set your flaps suitably for the conditions and runway length
				4. Release the parking brakes
				5. Apply throttle gently, until at 75% throttle
				6. Rotate at around 140-160kt
				7. Raise landing gear at positive climb
				8. Maintain positive climb

				Captain Notes:
				- Never reverse from terminal without aid from a pushback. It should be used until the aircraft is on the taxiway.
				- Ensure you allow enough room to manoeuvre around the airport, given that it is a long aircraft.
				- On a short or wet runway, flaps should be set lower on both landing and takeoff, and throttle set to full on takeoff.
				- There are risks of overrunning the runway apron upon landing and takeoff, aswell as overrunning the taxiway corners in the 767. In wet 					conditions especially; take care and ensure that the correct speed guidelines and height are maintained.
				- During turbulant conditions, The seatbelt warning sound should be initiated by the captain.

				=== Cruising ===
				Cruising Speed: Mach 0.80
				Service Ceiling: 42,000ft

				=== Landing ===
				1. Decend through 200kt, reaching roughly 160kt 1mile before reaching the apron
				2. set flaps accordingly
				3. Land at roughly 140kt, touch down carefully and smoothly at 135kt.
				4. Apply Speedbrakes
				5. Apply thrust reversal and apply throttle
				6. Lower throttle and deactivate thrust reversers
				7. If necessary, Emergency brakes should be used
			</text>

</PropertyList>

